Guide to The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings AIA.089
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings
1976-2001
1999-2000
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Flannelly, Adrian
Irish Radio Network USA
AIA.089
5.96 Linear Feet in 5 flat boxes and 2 cassette boxes
327 audiocassettes
Adrian Flannelly (1942-2024) was an Irish broadcaster; and the Chairman and CEO of Irish Radio Network USA. He hosted The Adrian Flannelly Show, a weekly radio program he began in 1969, which consisted of a combination of music; international and national news; cultural news; economic analysis and commentary; and interviews with writers, musicians, politicians, and other public figures. The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings consists of audiocassette recordings of his weekly Irish American talk radio program, dated approximately 1976-2001; and additional recordings, dated approximately 1983-2000.
Scope and Contents
The Adrian Flannelly Show Recordings consists of audiocassette recordings donated by Adrian Flannelly. The materials in the collection date from 1976 to 2001 with the bulk of materials dating 1999-2000. Series I: The Adrian Flannelly Show contains 395 episodes of Flannelly's weekly Irish American talk radio program, dated approximately 1976-2001. Flannelly's show consists of a combination of music; international and national news; cultural news; and economic analysis and commentary. Topics including immigration reform, visas for undocumented Irish youth, and the conflict in Northern Ireland were discussed frequently. The show also features interviews with writers, actors, musicians, politicians, and other public figures.
Series II: Additional Tapes, dated approximately 1983-2000, contains sound checks, event coverage, interviews, religious recordings, and music. These were donated by Flannelly, but their association with his radio program is unclear.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged into two series:
Series I: The Adrian Flannelly Show
Series II: Additional Tapes
Within each series, the episodes have been arranged in chronological order by air date. Undated material was arranged in alphabetical order when possible.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Adrian Flannelly in March 2020. The accession number associated with this gift is 2020.020.
Biographical Note
Adrian Flannelly (1942-2024) was an Irish broadcaster and the Chairman and CEO of Irish Radio Network USA. He was a native of Attymass, Co. Mayo in Ireland and emigrated to the United States in 1959 at seventeen years old. He hosted The Adrian Flannelly Show, a weekly radio program he began in 1969, which consisted of a combination of music; international and national news; cultural news; economic analysis and commentary; and interviews with writers, musicians, politicians, and other public figures. Flannelly used his radio show to highlight social and political issues concerning Irish and Irish American communities, including United States immigration reform; the Donnelly, Berman and Morrison visas programs for undocumented Irish youth; and and the conflict in Northern Ireland. He served as the Irish Cultural Liaison for the Irish Hunger Memorial in Battery Park City and assissted in the the construction of the memorial. Flannelly also received numerous honors from Irish and Irish American organizations in the greater New York City area including the Irish Echo's Irish American of the Year award. In 2016, was awarded an honorary Doctorate degree from Quinnipiac University; and in 2021, Flannelly was awarded the Irish government's highest honor, the Presidential Distinguished Service Award, acknowledging his work in Irish Community Support.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Appraisal
In 2021, seven duplicate tapes were deaccessioned from the collection.
In October 2025, 103 audiocassettes affected by mold were deaccessioned after digitization. Two blank tapes were also deaccessioned.
Radio programs.; Irish Americans -- Ethnic identity.; Irish Americans -- History.; Irish Americans -- New York (N.Y.); Irish Americans -- New York (State) -- New York -- Political activity.; Irish Americans -- Social life and customs.; Northern Ireland -- History -- 1968-1998; Peace movements -- Northern Ireland; Emigration and immigration law -- United States.; Radio broadcasters; Flannelly, Adrian
- Series I: The Adrian Flannelly Show, 1976-2001; 256 audiocassettes in 4 flatboxes
  Scope and Contents
  The Adrian Flannelly Show consisted of a combination of music; international and national news; cultural news; and economic analysis and commentary. Topics including community events; American-Irish relations; immigration reform; the Donnelly, Berman and Morrison visas programs for undocumented Irish youth; and the conflict in Northern Ireland were discussed frequently. The show also featured interviews with writers such as Malachy McCourt; actors such as Maureen O'Hara, Jim Flavin, and Ray Collins; movie producers such as Hal Roach; musicians such as Mickey Carton, Brendan Shine, Frank Patterson, Patrick (Pat) McGuigan, Dermot O'Brien, Paddy Noonan, Freddie White, and Gay McIntyre; politicians such as Pádraig MacKernan, Daithí Ó Ceallaigh, Mario Cuomo, and Charles Haughey; and other public figures such as Frank Durkin, Patrick Peyton, and Kevin O'Connor. This series contains 256 audiocassette recordings of Flannelly's radio program.
  - 1976, cuid43555
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 62 minutes
    Topics discussed in this episode include Irish Christmas and Fintan's House.
  - November 1977, cuid43556
  - September 1978, cuid43300
    Duration: 60 minutes
  - September 23-24, 1978, cuid43301
    Duration: 58 minutes
  - December 1, 1978, cuid43302
    Duration: 63 minutes
  - April 15, 1979, cuid43557
    Duration: 61 minutes
    This episode features Irish-American attorney, Frank Durkin. Topics discussed include Easter Sunday and Irish ballet.
  - December 20, 1981, cuid43558
    This episode includes a special holiday message and Christmas greeting.
  - 1983, cuid43559
    Duration: 126 minutes
  - April 30 - May 1, 1983, cuid43303 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0004)
    Duration: 89 minutes
  - June 4, 1983, cuid43304
    Duration: 90 minutes
  - August 15, 1983, cuid43560
    Duration: 5 minutes
    This episode features a brief public invitation to the Big Irish Fair at Coney Island.
  - September 24, 1983, cuid43305 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0006)
  - October 8, 1983, cuid43306 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0007)
    Duration: 59 minutes
  - October 29, 1983, cuid43307
  - November 5, 1983, cuid43308
  - December 3, 1983, cuid43309
    Duration: 87 minutes
  - December 10, 1983, cuid43310 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0012)
    Duration: 57 minutes
  - December 31, 1983, cuid43313
  - January 21, 1984, cuid43311
  - January 30, 1984, cuid43312
    Duration: 31 minutes
  - July 1984, cuid43563 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0265)
    This episode features Joe Murphy.
  - January 5, 1985, cuid43314
  - January 19, 1985, cuid43315
    Duration: 84 minutes
  - January 20, 1985, cuid43316
    Duration: 77 minutes
  - January 25, 1985, cuid43380
  - January 26, 1985, cuid43317
  - February 2, 1985, cuid43612
  - February 9, 1985, cuid43318 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0020)
    Duration: 93 minutes
  - February 10, 1985, cuid43377
    Duration: 55 minutes
  - February 23, 1985, cuid43319 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0021)
    Duration: 88 minutes
  - February 24, 1985, cuid43320
  - March 2, 1985, cuid43321
  - March 9, 1985, cuid43322 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0024)
    Duration: 94 minutes
  - March 10, 1985, cuid43323 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0025)
  - March 16, 1985, cuid43324 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0026)
  - March 23, 1985, cuid43325
  - March 24, 1985, cuid43326 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0028)
    Duration: 53 minutes
  - March 30, 1985, cuid43327 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0029)
  - April 6, 1985, cuid43328 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0030)
  - April 20, 1985, cuid43329 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0031)
  - April 27, 1985, cuid43330 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0032)
  - May 5, 1985, cuid43331
    Duration: 48 minutes
  - May 11, 1985, cuid43332 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0034)
  - May 17, 1985, cuid43333 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0035)
    Duration: 91 minutes
  - May 18, 1985, cuid43334
  - June 1, 1985, cuid43335 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0037)
  - June 2, 1985, cuid43336 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0038)
  - June 8, 1985, cuid43337
  - June 15, 1985, cuid43338 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0040)
    Duration: 93 min
  - June 16, 1985, cuid43339
  - June 22, 1985, cuid43340 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0042)
  - June 29, 1985, cuid43341 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0043)
  - August 3, 1985, cuid43342 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0044)
  - August 25, 1985, cuid43343
    Duration: 29 minutes
  - September 1985, cuid43564
    This episode features musician Dermot O'Brien. Topics discussed include the Great Irish Fair.
  - September 1, 1985, cuid43344 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0046)
    Duration: 32 minutes
  - September 1, 1985, cuid43345 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0047)
  - September 8, 1985, cuid43346 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0048)
  - September 8, 1985, cuid43347 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0049)
    Duration: 56 minutes
  - September 21, 1985, cuid43348
  - September 22, 1985, cuid43349
  - October 3, 1985, cuid43350
    Duration: 95 minutes
  - October 6, 1985, cuid43351 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0053)
  - October 12, 1985, cuid43565
    Duration: 65 minutes
  - October 19, 1985, cuid43352
  - October 20, 1985, cuid43353
  - November 2, 1985, cuid43355
  - November 9, 1985, cuid43354
    Duration: 86 minutes
  - November 16, 1985, cuid43356 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0058)
  - December 8, 1985, cuid43357 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0059)
  - December 15, 1985, cuid43358 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0060)
  - December 22, 1985, cuid43359; Duration: 41 minutes; Preservation Note: Side 2 of the tape is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0061)
  - January 1986, cuid43566
    This episode features singer Guss Hayes.
  - January 11, 1986, cuid43360 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0062)
  - January 19, 1986, cuid43361
  - January 25, 1986, cuid43362
  - January or February 1986, cuid43567 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0269)
    This episode features Irish Ambassador Pádraig MacKernan and movie producer Hal Roach.
  - February 1986, cuid43568 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0270)
    This episode features Malachy [unknown last name] and singer Brendan Shine.
  - February 1986, cuid43569 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0271)
    This episode features Malachy [unknown last name], musician Frank Patterson, and Suzanne Stein.
  - February 8, 1986, cuid43363 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0065)
  - February 15, 1986, cuid43364 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0066)
  - February 22, 1986, cuid43365
  - March 1986, cuid43366
  - March 1, 1986, cuid43367 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0069)
  - March 9, 1986, cuid43570 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0272)
  - March 16, 1986, cuid43368 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0070)
    Duration: 47 minutes; Preservation Note: Side 2 of the tape is blank.
  - March 29, 1986, cuid43369
  - April 5, 1986, cuid43370
  - April 5, 1986, cuid43371
  - April 5, 1986, cuid43372
  - April 12, 1986, 1985; cuid43373 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0075)
  - May 1986, cuid43571 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0273)
    This episode features musicians Pat McGuigan and Jimmy Kelly; Malachy [unknown last name]; and Dearie.
  - May 3, 1986, cuid43374
  - May 10, 1986, cuid43375 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0077)
  - May 25, 1986, cuid43573
    This episode features Deborah Snow performing the song "Battle of New Orleans."
  - June 28, 1986, cuid43376 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0078)
  - July 1986, cuid43574
    This episode features musicians Frank Noland and Mattie Connolly.
  - September 1986, cuid43575 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0277)
    This episode features Irish Fine Gael politician, Peter Barry. Topics discussed include the Stockton Wing Band.
  - December 1986, cuid43576
    This episode features actor Jim Flavin and pub owner Eamonn Doran. Topics discussed include the visa lottery.
  - December 6, 1986, cuid43577 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0279)
    Duration: 92 minutes
    This episode features musicians Freddie White, Paddy Noonan, Noel Kingston, and Ed McKenna. Topics discussed include the Irish Center.
  - January 1987, cuid43378
  - January 1987, cuid43578
    This episode features actress Maureen O'Hara. Topics discussed include a green card application campaign.
  - January 30, 1987, cuid43379
    Duration: 37 minutes
  - February 1987, cuid43579
    This episode features actors Jim Flavin and Ray Collins. Topics discussed include visas.
  - February 13, 1988, cuid43381
    Duration: 19 minutes
  - April 20, 1988, cuid43580
    Duration: 36 minutes
    This episode features former Taoiseach Charles Haughey.
  - May 27-30, 1988, cuid43581
  - January 2, 1999, cuid43382 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0084)
    Duration: 119 minutes
  - January 9, 1999, cuid43383 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0085)
    Duration: 121 minutes
  - January 10, 1999, cuid43384 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0086)
    Duration: 123 minutes
  - January 16, 1999, cuid43385 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0087)
  - January 17, 1999, cuid43386 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0088)
  - January 23, 1999, cuid43387 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0089)
  - January 24, 1999, cuid43388 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0090)
    Duration: 124 minutes
  - January 30, 1999, cuid43389 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0091)
  - January 31, 1999, cuid43390 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0092)
  - February 6, 1999, cuid43391 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0093)
  - February 7, 1999, cuid43392 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0094)
  - February 13, 1999, cuid43393 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0095)
    Duration: 122 minutes
  - February 14, 1999, cuid43394 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0096)
  - February 20, 1999, cuid43395 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0097)
    Duration: 25 minutes; Preservation Note: Side 2 of the tape is blank.
  - February 21, 1999, cuid43396 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0098)
    Duration: 117 minutes
  - February 27, 1999, cuid43397 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0099)
  - February 28, 1999, cuid43398 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0100)
    Duration: 116 minutes
  - March 6, 1999, cuid43399 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0101)
    Duration: 120 minutes
  - March 7, 1999, cuid43400 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0102)
  - March 13, 1999, cuid43401 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0103)
  - March 14, 1999, cuid43402 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0104)
  - March 20, 1999, cuid43403 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0105)
  - March 21, 1999, cuid43404 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0106)
  - March 27, 1999, cuid43405 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0107)
  - April 3, 1999, cuid43406 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0108)
  - April 4, 1999, cuid43407 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0109)
  - April 10, 1999, cuid43408 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0110)
  - April 11, 1999, cuid43409 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0111)
  - April 17, 1999, cuid43410 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0112)
  - April 18, 1999, cuid43411 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0113)
  - April 24, 1999, cuid43412 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0114)
    Duration: 118 minutes
  - April 25, 1999, cuid43413 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0115)
  - May 1, 1999, cuid43414 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0116)
  - May 2, 1999, cuid43415 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0117)
  - May 8, 1999, cuid43416 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0118)
  - May 9, 1999, cuid43417 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0119)
  - May 15, 1999, cuid43418 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0120)
  - May 16, 1999, cuid43419 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0121)
  - May 22, 1999, cuid43420 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0122)
  - May 23, 1999, cuid43421 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0123)
  - May 29, 1999, cuid43422 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0124)
  - May 30, 1999, cuid43423 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0125)
  - June 5, 1999, cuid43424 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0126)
  - June 6, 1999, cuid43425 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0127)
  - June 12, 1999, cuid43426 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0128)
  - June 13, 1999, cuid43427 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0129)
  - June 19, 1999, cuid43428 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0130)
  - June 20, 1999, cuid43429 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0131)
  - June 26, 1999, cuid43430 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0132)
  - June 27, 1999, cuid43431 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0133)
  - July 3, 1999, cuid43432 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0134)
  - July 4, 1999, cuid43433 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0135)
  - July 10, 1999, cuid43434 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0136)
  - July 11, 1999, cuid43435 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0137)
  - July 17, 1999, cuid43436 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0138)
  - July 18, 1999, cuid43437 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0139)
  - July 24, 1999, cuid43438 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0140)
  - July 25, 1999, cuid43439 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0141)
  - July 31, 1999, cuid43440 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0142)
  - August 1, 1999, cuid43441 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0143)
  - August 7, 1999, cuid43442 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0144)
  - August 8, 1999, cuid43443 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0145)
  - August 14, 1999, cuid43444 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0146)
  - August 15, 1999, cuid43445 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0147)
  - August 22, 1999, cuid43446 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0148)
  - August 28, 1999, cuid43447 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0149)
  - September 4, 1999, cuid43448 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0150)
  - September 5, 1999, cuid43449 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0151)
  - September 11, 1999, cuid43450 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0152)
  - September 12, 1999, cuid43451 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0153)
  - September 18, 1999, cuid43452 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0154)
  - September 19, 1999, cuid43453 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0155)
  - September 25, 1999, cuid43454 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0156)
  - September 26, 1999, cuid43455 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0157)
  - October 2, 1999, cuid43456 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0158)
  - October 3, 1999, cuid43457 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0159)
  - October 9, 1999, cuid43458 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0160)
  - October 10, 1999, cuid43459 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0161)
  - October 16, 1999, cuid43460 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0162)
  - October 17, 1999, cuid43461 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0163)
  - October 23, 1999, cuid43462 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0164)
  - October 24, 1999, cuid43463 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0165)
  - October 30, 1999, cuid43464 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0166)
  - November 6, 1999, cuid43465 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0167)
  - November 7, 1999, cuid43466 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0168)
    Duration: 114 minutes
  - November 13, 1999, cuid43467 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0169)
  - November 14, 1999, cuid43468 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0170)
  - November 20, 1999, cuid43469 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0171)
  - November 21, 1999, cuid43470 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0172)
  - November 27, 1999, cuid43471 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0173)
  - December 4, 1999, cuid43472 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0174)
  - December 5, 1999, cuid43473 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0175)
  - December 11, 1999, cuid43474 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0176)
  - December 12, 1999, cuid43475 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0177)
    Duration: 107 minutes
  - December 18, 1999, cuid43476 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0178)
  - December 25, 1999, cuid43477 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0179)
    Duration: 59 minutes; Preservation Note: Side 2 of the tape is blank.
  - December 25, 1999, cuid43478 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0180)
    Duration: 66 minutes
  - December 26, 1999, cuid43479 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0181)
  - December 26, 1999, cuid43480 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0182)
  - December 28, 1999, cuid43481 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0183)
  - January 1, 2000, cuid43482 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0184)
  - January 2, 2000, cuid43483 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0185)
  - January 8, 2000, cuid43484 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0186)
  - January 15, 2000, cuid43485 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0187)
  - January 16, 2000, cuid43486 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0188)
  - January 23, 2000, cuid43487 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0189)
  - January 29, 2000, cuid43488 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0190)
  - February 5, 2000, cuid43489 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0191)
  - February 6, 2000, cuid43490 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0192)
    Duration: 125 minutes
  - February 12, 2000, cuid43491 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0193)
  - February 13, 2000, cuid43492 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0194)
  - February 19, 2000, cuid43493 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0195)
  - February 26, 2000, cuid43494 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0196)
  - February 27, 2000, cuid43495 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0197)
  - March 4, 2000, cuid43496 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0198)
  - March 5, 2000, cuid43497 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0199)
  - March 11, 2000, cuid43498 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0200)
  - March 12, 2000, cuid43499 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0201)
  - March 17, 2000, cuid43584 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0286)
    Topics discussed include St. Patrick's Day.
  - March 19, 2000, cuid43500 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0202)
  - March 26, 2000, cuid43501 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0203)
  - April 1, 2000, cuid43502 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0204)
  - April 2, 2000, cuid43503 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0205)
  - April 8, 2000, cuid43504 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0206)
  - April 9, 2000, cuid43505 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0207)
  - April 15, 2000, cuid43506 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0208)
  - April 16, 2000, cuid43507 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0209)
  - April 22, 2000, cuid43508 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0210)
  - April 23, 2000, cuid43509 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0211)
  - April 29, 2000, cuid43510 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0212)
  - April 30, 2000, cuid43511 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0213)
    Duration: 67 minutes
  - May 6, 2000, cuid43512 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0214)
  - May 7, 2000, cuid43513 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0215)
  - May 13, 2000, cuid43514 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0216)
  - May 14, 2000, cuid43515 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0217)
  - May 20, 2000, cuid43516 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0218)
  - May 21, 2000, cuid43517 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0219)
  - May 27, 2000, cuid43518 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0220)
  - May 28, 2000, cuid43519 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0221)
  - June 3, 2000, cuid43520 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0222)
  - June 10, 2000, cuid43521 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0223)
  - June 17, 2000, cuid43522 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0224)
  - June 18, 2000, cuid43523 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0225)
  - June 24, 2000, cuid43524
  - June 25, 2000, cuid43525 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0227)
  - July 1, 2000, cuid43526 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0228)
  - July 8, 2000, cuid43527 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0229)
  - July 15, 2000, cuid43528 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0230)
  - July 22, 2000, cuid43529 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0231)
  - July 29, 2000, cuid43530 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0232)
    Duration: 112 minutes
  - August 5, 2000, cuid43531 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0233)
  - August 12, 2000, cuid43532 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0234)
  - August 19, 2000, cuid43533 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0235)
  - August 26, 2000, cuid43534 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0236)
  - September 2, 2000, cuid43535 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0237)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation Note: Side 2 of the tape is blank.
  - September 9, 2000, cuid43536 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0238)
  - September 16, 2000, cuid43537 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0239)
  - September 23, 2000, cuid43538 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0240)
  - September 30, 2000, cuid43539 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0241)